

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Jakarta Metropolitan Area Indonesia +6281357202812 stanlyskwok@gmail.com

Links

Personal Website
LinkedIn

Skills

JavaScript

Solidity

Flutter

React

Node.js

Next JS

Express JS

PostgreSQL

TypeScript

Hardhat

MongoDB

Profile

Hello, I'm a full-stack Web, Mobile and Web3 Developer. I specialize in using React for Web Development, Flutter & React Native for Mobile development and React & Solidity for Web3 Development. I use Node JS for backend development, and PostgreSQL as the database.

Go to this website to view my portfolio: https://stanly-sukmajaya.vercel.app/

Employment History

Full Stack Developer, Metabase, Jakarta

JANUARY 2023 - APRIL 2023

Responsibilities:

- Developing and maintaining scalable and efficient frontend architectures that support the development of high-quality web or mobile applications.
- Collaborating with designers, developers, and stakeholders to develop functional and intuitive user interfaces.
- Writing clean and maintainable code that is scalable, efficient, and adheres to established coding standards.
- Troubleshooting and debugging code to ensure that web applications work smoothly and efficiently.
- Managing and optimizing mobile application build processes, including the use of task runners, bundlers, and preprocessors.
- Integrating frontend code with backend systems, including APIs and databases.
- Developing and maintaining decentralized applications (dApps) on blockchain platforms.

Flutter Developer, Adira Finance, Jakarta

AUGUST 2021 - DECEMBER 2022

Responsibilities:

- Developing mobile apps and web applications for Adira's internal use.
- Developing and maintaining scalable and efficient frontend architectures that support the development of high-quality mobile applications.
- Collaborating with designers, developers, and stakeholders to develop functional and intuitive user interfaces.
- Writing clean and maintainable code that is scalable, efficient, and adheres to established coding standards.
- Troubleshooting and debugging code to ensure that web or mobile applications work smoothly and efficiently.
- Integrating frontend code with backend systems, including APIs and databases.

Certifications

Full Stack JavaScript Immersive Program, Hacktiv8, Jakarta, Indonesia

NOVEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2021

Graduated with 98.41% final grade.

Learned full-stack web & mobile app development.

Learned how to build a fully-functioning web and mobile apps from scratch.

Programming Language: JavaScript

Front-end: HTML, CSS, Vue.js, React.js

Back-end: Node.js, Express.js

Database: PostgreSQL

Education

Bachelor of Business (Accountancy), Auckland, New Zealand

FEBRUARY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2019